NEIL ALVAREZ GARCIA

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER

PROFESSIONAL RESUME

I am a Full-Stack Developer with three years of experience, who is constantly striving to learn and improve both professionally and personally. I enjoy challenging myself with emerging technologies and staying up to date with the latest trends in the industry.

PROFESSIONAL HABILITIES

FRONT-END:

- -HTML5
- -CSS3 (Bootstrap, tailwind and SASS)
- -JAVASCRIPT, TYPESCRIPT
- -REACT.JS, NEXTJS

BACK-END:

- -JAVASCRIPT, TYPESCRIPT
- -NODEJS, EXPRESS, GRAPHQL
- -MONGODB, MYSQL, POSTGRESQL

ANOTHER TECHNOLOGIES:

- -DOCKER
- -GIT
- -TESTING WITH JEST

OTHER SKILLS:

- -ENGLISH, SPANISH
- -GOOD WORKING AT A TEAM AND UNDER PRESURE, LEADERSHIP, MENTORING, FAST AND SELF LEARNER

CONTACT ME

Email: Neil8b.jjr2014@gmail.com Cellphone: +57-3024151956

EXPERIENCES

SOFTWARE FULL-STACK DEVELOPER

WebRun Agency | November 2022 - Current

I am responsible for creating, reviewing code, assisting others, and fixing the landing pages and forms that WebRun provides to its clients. I work closely with the design, front-end, and sales teams to ensure that we deliver high-quality products and services.:

- I integrated all the repositories into a monorepo to reduce bloat and eliminate duplicate code..
- I helped improve client confidentiality by creating fast and efficient web applications with tracked data forms.
- I created different widgets for the web apps, making it easier for users to see the quality of our work.

SOFTWARE FRONTEND DEVELOPER

GreenRun | April 2022 to November 2022

With the design, frontend, and QA teams, I was in charge of creating, improving, and fixing the app that GreenRun offers to users for betting.

- I integrated a new library into the app, improving its loading time and reducing its weight.
- I created a web app from scratch that allowed influencers to create links for current bets, which they could share with their followers. This helped improve the number of users who were betting
- I created different widgets for the app, upgrading and improving the user experience of the application.

SOFTWARE FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Televisa Univision | January 2022 to June 2022

With the front-end team, I was responsible for maintaining the Univision website, fixing the bugs that used to appear every day and adding assets to it.:

- I maintained all the views for the shows, news, and sports pages that the Univision website has.
- I improved the way Univision was displaying PDFs on their website, making them load faster for the users.

ACADEMIC TRAINING

VIRTUAL COURSES, FORUMS AND DOCUMENTATIONS

SOFTWARE WEB DEVELOPMENT

- -HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, tailwind and SASS
- -JAVASCRIPT, TYPESCRIPT
- -React.js, Nextjs
- -Nodejs, Express, Graphql
- -MongoDB, Mysql, Postgresql
- -Jest and Unit Testing
- -Git and Docker
- English